if Putin were a worthy president
если бы Путин был достойным президентом
he would protect the whole nation he would be a
он бы всю нацию бы защищал он бы
nationalist that's how it works in America
националист вот как работает в Америке
like in the European Union Yes nationalism there
как вот в Евросоюзе Да национализм там
categories are immediately legislated and Putin is
категори сразу их законодательно а Путин
silent That's why
же молчит Поэтому вот это вот поэтому
people are like sheep you know and Putin is a
люди люди как бараны понимаешь а Путин
shepherd Shepherd that's it  so says and the rams
Пастух Пастух вот так говорит и бараны
here follow you understand Russian
вот следуют понимаешь русский
rams Salam aleikum brothers
бараны Салам алейкум братья
Assalam aleikum you are from Kyrgyzstan
Ассалам алейкум ты из Кыргызстана
Kazakhstan
Казахстана
where from Kyrgyzstan
откуда из Кыргызстана
Bishkek Bishkek Oh My grandmother Labada I am
Бишкек Бишкек О У меня бабушка Лабада Я
also
тоже
Kyrgyz I am Kyrgyz Yes but it turns out my
Кыргыз я Кыргыз Да но у меня получается
father is Ukrainian And my
отец украинец А
mother I don't understand
мама понима не понимаю у
Yes I am
Да я
Stan
Стан
Stan  I
Стан всё
probably read all this to me in childhood
наверна читала мне в детстве
probably Russians Yes Russians don't
наверно русских Да русские нас не
respect us they say that we are
уважают они говорят что мы
crazy
поехавшие
I am from the
я с
root Yes they always I fought for this I
корня Да они всегда я за это дрался я
worked there in Moscow as a courier some guy
там в Москве работал курьером какой-то
drove up my car there was a jam and I
подъехал мою машину затора нел и обратно
go back out and he comes to me  he drives up,
выхожу и он ко мне подъезжает
come on over and says,
подходи и говорит
oh, the Tajiks have come, wash me
э понаехали таджики ты мою машину
scratched the car park the car I tell him
поцарапал Поставь машину я я ему говорю
you came here we fly here on
это ты сюда понаехал мы сюда летаем на
planes you are the main thing drove up scratched my car
самолётах ты главно подъехал мою машину
did everything yourself p I admit at
поцарапал всё сделал сам п я призн на
work work here you tell
работе работай тут ты
me Salam what do you want to say you are a son
мне Салам что хочешь сказать ты сын
and it turns out that my mother is Kyrgyz
и у меня получается у меня мама кыргызка
and  my father is Ukrainian and I look more like my father
а отец украинец и я больше На отца похож
and but when they find out that my mother is
да и но когда узнают что у меня мама
Kyrgyz I also always beat
кыргызка тоже такая я тоже бил всегда
when
когда
we talk Listen, why do you have
говорим Слушай а почему у тебя сзади
this European behind you Yes, and I live in the
этот Европейский Да фо А я живу в
European Union Now I live in the European Union
Евросоюзе Сейчас я живу в Евросоюзе Да
Yes, and A  where exactly is Brussels And in Brussels,
вот а А где именно Брюссель А в Брюсселе
yes,
да
cool, cool markets And you are also from Bishkek
круто круто базары А ты тоже из Бишкека
Well, yes, by the way Well, as I understand it, yes Well, as I
Ну да кста Ну я как понял да Ну я как
understand it Yes, you don’t respect Russians I don’t
понял Да ты русских не уважаешь не
respect They, they don’t look I’m half
уважаю Они они не смотри я наполовину
Ukrainian and half Kyrgyz they don’t
украинец наполовину Кыргыз они не
respect either Kyrgyz or Russians  Yes, they
уважают ни кыргызов не русских Да они
all say that we you In short, you
все говорят что мы вас Короче вы
were some kind of wild, we taught you everything,
какие-то дикие были мы вас всё научили
they don’t know, and when did the Russians even  toads
они не знают да когда у русских ещё жабы
croaked in the swamps the Kyrgyz already had a
квакали в болотах у кыргыза уже было и
Letter and a state we had
Письмо было и государство было мы
Great Asia and the Kyrgyz and Uzbeks and
Великая Азия была и киргизы и узбеки и
Kazakhs all were yes we
казахи все были да
came in droves I told him My grandfather
ны понаехали я я ему сказал Мой дед тут
fought here everyone fought here so here I am Look
воевал тут все воевали так вот я Смотри
when there was a war with Hitler the Russians  5
когда была с Гитлером война русских 5
million surrendered to Hitler and then here is
млн сдались в плен Гитлеру и потом вот
Vlasov's army Yes, these were all Russians
армия Власова да Это ж все русские были
who shot our grandfathers, Kyrgyz and Ukrainians,
которые нашим дедам кыргыза украинцам
in the back Yes, and now they are shouting,
стреляли в спину Да а они сейчас кричат
raise the flag, put it there, Kazakh, Kazakh, yes,
флаг поднял там постави казах казах да
yes, and they say that it is Russian
да а они говорят что это русский
Yes, yusu asusu, here he put it  flag Here is a
Да юсу асусу вот он поставил флаг Вот
Russian not a Ukrainian nothing purely Asian
русский не украинец ничего чисто азиат
He put it there they
Он поставил там это они
forgot Kazakhs in Uzbeks died against
забыли казахов в узбеках умерла против
Hitler although we did not have
Гитлера хотя у нас не было в Кыргызстане
this war in Kyrgyzstan Kazakhstan Yes Russians took
Казахстане этой войны Да русские брали
our grandfathers threw them like in assaults like
наших дедов бросали вот как в штурмы как
now they just threw them without anything
сейчас просто бросали без ничего
poured the first Redi A  and when When
наливали первый Реди А и когда Когда на
I have I just have a great-grandfather and he himself is from
у меня У меня просто прадед да он сам из
kok-yangak you know Kok
кок-янгак знаешь Кок
Yangak
Янгак
region from there they sent him, that means uh
область оттуда его отправили значит ээ
he fought near Kursk he was
воевать он под Курском воевал был
wounded they brought him to Moscow to the
раненный привезли его в Москву в
hospital and he sees all the Muscovites
госпиталь и он смотрит все москвичи
walking around cafes they have theaters and he
гуляют кафешек у них театры и он такой
says they took me from Kok Yangak Yes he
меня из Кок Янгак забрали говорит Да он
told me they took them away  through
мне рассказывал забрали повезли через
there 5,000 km so that I die somewhere in
там 5.000 км чтобы я умирал где-то в
Kursk Yes and they are now and it is happening
Курске Да а они сейчас так и происходит
now the same
сейчас так же само
thing right now the same thing Therefore yes it is It has always
сечас самое Поэтому да это Это всегда
been like this just these Russians they are
так было просто вот этот русские они
Nazis they divide people you are Tajik You are
нацисты они делят людей ты ты таджик Ты
Russian I am now in Europe  I'll go they don't
русский Я сейчас в Европу поеду они не
know they have no
знают у них
concept Andrey Andrey Andryu Listen are you
поняти Андрей Андрей Андрю Слушай ты
religious you no no I'm
религиозный ты нет нет я
secular se atheist Well, my
светский све атеист Да ну у меня у меня
great-grandfather he was Also religious but
прадед он был Ещё религиозный но
not me I don't understand these I
не я как бы я не разбираюсь в эти Я
just don't believe in anything you nobody  I'm not
просто ни в что не верю тебя никто не
going to accuse at all, I'm just
собирается обвинять вообще просто я тебя
asking you, are you Orthodox at all,
спрашиваю ты православный ли вообще
no one at all, Niko Okay, okay, it's just
никакой вобще Нико Окей хорошо просто
business  that's what you're
дело в том то что сейчас вы сейчас
saying now about the Russians being so
говорите вот насчёт то что русские такие
skanky Yes, I don't like Russians either
ские Да я русских тоже как бы не люблю
Yes, because in St. Petersburg there is a law,
Да потому что впитере закон
I studied there for 5 years and that's why I know
я там 5 лет учился и поэтому я знаю
what they are like,
какие они
they're just Nazis, I'll say that
просто они нацисты я те так
in NT they are like that  Nobody there You are Russian
такие в НТ ля Никто там Ты русский
Why do you know
жл Почему знае
Why nobody
Почему никто
Neva was a worthy president a long time ago
Нева давно давно н был достойным
he would have protected the whole nation
президентом он бы всю нацию бы защищал
he would have been a nationalist that's how it works in
он бы националист вот как работает в
America like in the European Union Yes
Америке как вот в Евросоюзе Да
nationalism there are categories immediately
национализм там категори сразу их
legislated and Putin is silent That's why
законодательно а Путин же молчит Поэтому
this is why  people people are like sheep
вот это вот поэтому люди люди как бараны
you know and Putin is a Shepherd Shepherd speaks like this
понимаешь а Путин Пастух Пастух вот так
and the sheep follow you know
говорит и бараны вот следуют понимаешь
Russian sheep Well, like us too, sheep
русские бараны Ну как и мы тоже бараны
Like us And who are you St. Petersburg don't listen to I
Как нам А ты на кого СПб не слушай Я
studied in accounting Yes Finance Putin
учился в бухгалтерии Да Финан тин Путин
there is a decree he didn't give a decree Yes it is necessary  will give
там указ указ он не давал Да надо даст
him an order him this is only Russian
указ ему ему это только только русский
he he didn't say so he won't give an order
он он так не говорил он не будет указ
this to everyone here Russian here you and
давать это каждому вот Русский вот нас с
I they will consider non-Russians this is not
тобой они посчитают нерусскими это не
Russian this is you are not a person  and if you are
русский это ты не человек а если ты
Russian you are a person if you are not
русский это ты человек если ты не
Russian
русский
They have such concepts Yes and here we have
У них такие понятия Да а у нас вот
Russians walking they are their
русские ходят они же их
wives are the same person that we have been with them since childhood you have
жен же чело что мы с детстве сним вы у
a lot of Russian classmates
нас реально много Одноклассников руски
Classmates whom we love I
Одноклассников которых мы любим Я их
respect them my classmates Yes  with whom
уважаю моих одноклассников Да с которыми
I studied together Well this is 20 to these are
Я учился вместе Ну это 20 к это
millions of millions of dollars Yes Russian boards
миллионы миллионные име Да доски русские
So my brother treats me The main thing in Kyrgyzstan is
Так относится брат мо главное в Киргизии
you Nobody
тебя Никто не
offends boards
обижает доски
in ro
в ро
offend you
обижайте
know look in Kyrgyzstan Yes right
знаешь смотри в Кыргызстане Да вот
now the Russians came to Kyrgyzstan
сейчас же русские приехали в Кыргызстан
Yes When they have mobilization nobody to them  didn't
да Когда у них мобилизация им никто не
say come Yes Live work oh and have
говорил приезжайте Да Живите работай о а
you seen the videos some of them start
вы видели ролики они некоторые начинают
that you don't want to serve me
что вы меня не хотите обслужить
in Russian they came to a foreign country Yes
по-русски они приехали в чужую страну Да
when they were in
они когда в
Russia They say you came in droves yes And
России Они говорят вы понаехали да А
now they came to Kyrgyzstan and they go
теперь приехали в Кыргызстан и они ходят
Come on in short to me damn  learn p words of mouth
Давай короче мне блин выучи п слов уст
Daru
Дару
stopped Russian yes Russian My grandfather for
переставал русский да русский Мой дед за
Russians there was Berlin there Red
русских там Берлин был там Красная
Moscow Russian
Москва руский
everything come on
всё давай
yes and you too yes come on And you me  water water
да а ты тоже да давай А ты я водичку
Okay, come on, come on, well, for being
водичка А ну давай давай ну за то что
Russian I'll definitely drink some water I'm
русский выпью водичку обязательно я я я
Russian I won't help Russians at all
русский я русским вообще не буду
if something touches me
помогать если что-то коснётся я украинцу
I'll help a Ukrainian I'll help a Ukrainian
я украинцу помогу
I'll say
я скажу Так
So, I'm half Kyrgyz and
что я вот сколько я наполовину Кыргыз
half Ukrainian Yes, I'll never  the
наполовину украинец Да мне никогда ни
Kyrgyz never said that I was somehow
киргизы не сказали что я какой-то не
different, the Ukrainians never said that the
такой никогда украинцы не сказали что
Nazis were normal at all, I think so too,
нацисты вообще нормально я Я вот тоже
and the Ukrainians think so, yes, they are not
вот думаю да и украинца думаю да они не
Nazis, if tomorrow I fly to Ukraine, I
нацисты если завтра я в Украину полечу
probably think that they will not tell
наверно думаю чтобы они Они не скажут
me that I am a
мне
Tajik,
таджик
they are not a magician  they will say I think they are
маджик они не скажут Я думаю они более
already more adequate already more they are the same
уже адекватны уже более они так так же
as Kazakhs already meeting you meet
как казахов уже встреча встречаешь
Kazakhs None of the Kazakhs will
казахов Никто из казахов тебе плохого
say a bad word to you Russians are immediately there thousands and you
слова не скажет русские сразу там тыщ а
also know how they do look They
ещё знаешь как они делают смотри Они
make films and in the films there is always a
снимают фильмы и в фильмах всегда
Russian like he is good  yeah and who's
русский типа он э хороший да а кто-то
there Tajik Uzbek Kyrgyz Kazakh they're
там таджик узбек ыргыз казах они
some kind of bad That's what I don't like yeah
какие-то пло Вот это мне не нравится да
Why are they filming
Поче они снима
it really is Why do they because
это действительно Почему они потому что
they are doing this Nazism on purpose that is
они специально делают этот нацизм что
wrong It is Putin you understand and people
неправильно Это Путин понимаешь а люди
swallow it it is people swallow it understand NN
это хавают это люди это хавают понима НН
wants everywhere and in all humanity
хочет б везде и во всём человечестве
for everyone to live well And look there is a
чтоб каждый жил хорошо Да и смотришь там
pensioner digging garbage I lived in Moscow for years
пенсионер мусор копать я года жил же в
Russian movies right past you drive by an
российские фильмы прямо мимо проезжаешь
old lady there pension is not enough she is digging not enough for them Here they are They don't respect old people they don't
Стариков не уважают они вот матерей не
respect mothers they don't respect grandfathers and here they
уважают они вот дедушек не уважают и тут
ram and then when you go to Europe
таранят та а вот в Европу поедешь
they stvo
они
this [ __ ] Russian Federation
ству вот это сру Российская Федерация
this [ __ ]  budget for this
вот это вот бюджет к этому
film there is a script if you know
фильму там идёт сценарий если ты в курсе
yes how is the meaning of the film what How do they watch Do they
да как значение фильма что Как смотрят
need to sponsor No well yes And they
Нужно ли спонсировать Не ну да И вот
see that it is whatever is necessary for the
видят то что это угодно для
legislation whatever is necessary for Putin
законодательства угодно Путину
sponsors Sk how many millions are there
спонсирует Ско сколько там миллионов
to make a film you know how do they watch They
чтобы фильм сня по знаешь как смотри Они
they like  now they say there are these
они типа вот сейчас говорят там вот эти
migrants who have come there, there are no jobs, but they
мигранты понаехали нет рабо Так они же
don't want to work, why do our brothers
не хотят работать Почему наши братья
work,
работают
why do they work in construction, why is there snow?  they
Почему работают на стройки Почему снег
clean because Russians are lazy, I
убирают потому что русские лентяи это я
know they don't want to. Yes, they don't want to
знаю они не хотят Да они не хотят за эти
clean up the trash for that kind of money,
деньги вот так вот мусор убирать они
even if they let them work, they
даже если даже позволят им работать они
won't
не
cope. You know why, because they're
справится знаешь почему потому что они
weaklings. That's what they do with these people.
слабаки вот вот это вот с этими
They get drunk on Friday and start Nava.
они напиваются пятницу начинают Нава
I I know the history The history means that a
я Я знаю историю Историю значит у
friend's father runs a construction company
знакомого отец он строительную фирму
Yes, he also had Tajiks and
держит Да у него были тоже там таджики
Kyrgyz there Well, in short, all sorts of guys from
киргизы Ну короче всякие ребята из
Asia came, in short, some kind of this Russian
Азии пришли короче какие-то это русская
community says that you are not
община говорит что вот ты не
patriotic because you don't
патриотичный потому что русских не
hire Russians Yes, in short, what-  then they
нанимает Да короче что-то там через
put a little pressure on him through the deputy, he Okay,
депутата немножко его надавили он Окей
good, yeah, he fired them, hired
хорошо Да он короче уволил этих набрал
Russians, in short, after 2 days, there
русских короче через 2 дня у него на
was just hell at his construction site, drunks, in short,
стройке просто жесть была пьяные короче
yes, one drunk, in short, fell from a crane,
да оди один пьяный короче с крана упал
like they drank it up, in short, a concrete mixer,
типа там пропили короче бетономешалку
in short, they took it and sold it to someone, damn  it's
короче взяли продали кому-то блин там
just brutal there,
жесть просто всё
he threw everyone out again, recruited the guys from
он выкинул всех снова набрал ребят
Tajikistan, Uzbekistan, Kyrgyzstan and
Таджикистан Узбекистан Кыргызстан и
says all these work, these understand,
говорит всё эти работают эти понимают
they came Yes, they came to work,
они приехали Да они приехали работать
they came to drink Yes, it's not just  They can
они бухать Да не просто Они могут тебе
entertain you Yes they work they work
развлечься Да они работа они работя
you know how that's
знаешь как вот
why look at us Kyrgyz Yes since
почему смотри у нас киргизов Да с
childhood as a child he already did something
детства как ребёнок он уже что-то делал
True he
Правда он
either PAZ horses yes or collected something
либо коней ПАЗ да либо что-то собирал
or Well he hunted already little where
либо Ну охотился он уже маленький де у
Russian he already  somewhere for some reason
русский он уже гдето почему-то
he is already shorter up to 25
уже он короче до 25
years old and the Russian is 253 years old he lives with his mother and
лет а русскому 253 лет он с мамой и
grandmother he lives with his mother 20 lives with his mother
бабушкой жит с мамой живёт 20 с мамой
What is this for him like a bathroom yes then he
жить Это что за ему как ванной да то он
can only bring a chick and bringing a chick is not an
может только братан а тёлку привести не
option at all on the balcony
вариант вообще на балконе
the chick says mom  Go get some bread
тёлку говорит мама Сходи за хлебом
Yes, I got it Yes So it's cool there
Да понял да Так что есть классно там ну
Well,
вот
first this
сначала этот
first
сначала
this when the war started And my
вот когда вот война вот начиналась И мне
friend came up to me
вот друг подошёл
Putin said in 30 minutes all of Ukraine
Путин сказал за 30 минут вся Украина не
will not be 100% That's it, don't ram I
будет 100% Вот так не тарань Я ему
tell him my brother This Russian one
говорю брат мой Вот этот российский
officer or
офицер либо
soldier he has Ber 100 bucks is worth
солдат у него Бер 100 баксов стоит
bucks T This is much more important in this
у баксов Т Это намного зает в этой
war Don't
войне Не
rush nuclear nya no don't rush this is
торопись ядерный ня не не торопись это
our
заша
BT we are  they argued with him and now it's been the
БТ мы с ним поспорили и сейчас вот
third or fourth year already the war is going on
третий или четвёртый год уже Война идёт
I told him then the
Я ему тогда
level yes
уров да у
they have them like beggars they stand like
них их как нищ они стоят как Оборванные
some ragged Ukrainian ones on the video as
какие-то на видео украинские такие как
if you know there are warriors of the Roman Empire you
будто знаешь там воины Римской империи
know beautiful yes there are girls
такие знаешь красиво да там девчонки
wanting to be with them  take a photo this is the
хотят с ними сфотографироваться это
Russian army like some kind of just
русская армия как какие-то просто там
show off show off bro this is show off
показуха показуха братан это показуха
just show off this is the Soviet Union They
просто показу это Советский Союз Они там
stayed there just stayed there
остались просто там остались
this is
это
modern modern technology
современные современная техника
anyway reliable it
по-любому же надёжная же она всегда
will always be how to say know
будет как сказать зна
Russians They constantly say here
е русские Постоянно говорят вот там вот
this  Kyrgyzstan Uzbekistan - these are poor
это Кыргызстан Узбекистан - это бедные
countries And why not poor because the
страны А почему не бедные потому что
Russian Empire Soviet Union
Российская империя Советский Союз
took all the resources from there Yes what was the
забирали оттуда все ресурсы Да что было
Soviet Union from Kyrgyzstan
Советский Союз из у Кыргызстана золото
had gold and there they whined Yes and metals There is the
было да там на и скули Да и металлы Там
entire periodic table Yes they pumped out they
вся таблица Менделеева Да они выкачивали
why didn't they give Lena a way  so that the
они почему Лену дорогу не для того чтобы
Kyrgyz would roll and so that the
киргизы катали а для того чтобы
tova Earlier Earlier Yes they thought so but
това Раньше Раньше Да так думали но
now I think yes the Kazakhs will now
сейчас вот я думаю да казахи сейчас
tell the Russians brother my brother
русским скажут брат братец мой
sort it out there  we'll stand here and
разбирайтесь там мы вот тут постоим
something will happen we'll support you or
что-то будет Мы вас поддержим или что-то
say something and we also have politics our
скажем и у нас тоже политика тоже наш
president says we're
президент говорит мы
supporters we won't fight no Yes we'll do it
сторонники мы не будем воевать не Да мы
like this we'll get better
будем вот так порон будем налаживаться
we'll
будем
watch I'll go for Russia and
смотреть Я сейчас за за Россию поеду и
for  I won't fight Ukraine, that's what I'll say,
за Украину не буду воевать вот так скажу
yes, yes, because Russia
да да Потому что потому что Россия
first wanted the Otkrytia, this is
сначала хотела чтобы одкб это ж
Kyrgyzstan, Armenia, Belarus, to take and
Кыргызстан Армения Белорусь взяли и
fight together with it against Ukraine, yes, it
воевали вместе с ней против Украины Да
wanted to involve, yes, and why, you know, so
хотела втянуть да А зачем понимаешь Так
you, guys, you
вы Ребята вы
need it, it's
он нужен
true, right now, here we are, here
правда сечас вот у нас вот
this is what
это чему
Here is how
Вот как
fairy tales
сказа
Russian speaking countries we
чные рко язычные страны сес
understand Uzbeks also understand with
понимаем узбеками тоже понимаем с
Cossacks is developing
казач развивается
probably will rise and say Putin
наверное поднимется и скажет Путин у
you have already sat your prokha better
тебя ты свою уже проха просидел лучше
Go away we will figure out ourselves what have you
Уйди мы сами разберёмся что ты тут уже
been sitting here too long Better go away dahom yes that's how we
Засиделся Отойди лучше дахом да вот так
will say Yes
скажем Да
that's what I hope  Yes, on Turan Yes, I
вот я надеюсь Да на Туран Да вот я на
don’t rely on Russians or Americans Yes,
русских на на американцев не надеюсь Да
I rely on Turan I hope the
вот я на Туран Надеюсь
Turkic-speaking republic is there too yes  look
тюркоязычный республика там же да смотри
this is also Sakha this is also like yes uh
это также Саха это ж тоже типа да э
Turkic language Are they Turks Sakha Yes
Турко язычный Они что же тюрки Саха Да
Sakha Altaians Kazakhs Uzbeks Kyrgyz
Саха алтайцы казахи узбеки кыргызы
Khakass these are huge territories Yes this
хакасы это огромные территории Да это
was all Uh Great Turan was Yes
всё было Э Великий Туран был Да вот
then the Russian Empire came and
потом Российская империя пришла
captured it's
захватила
amazing that you are naked bosses and beggars Yes
поразка что вы голые боссы и нищие Да
killed all the intelligentsia all the uns before
убило всех интеллигенцию всех ун до
this nskan Yes, nskan ruled yes
этого нскан Да вот нскан правил да
completely Central Asia that's where
полностью Средняя Азия вот где вот
Russia was there they ruled then Rus and
Россия была там они правили потом Русь и
after Rusia probably thinks Turkestan Yes it
после Русия наверное думает Туркестан Да
will be like that yes So yes it is
будет походу да вот так да Так что да
necessary there because Moscow yes Moscow
там нужно потому что Москва да Москва
too  who organized Khan Migu Timur
тоже кто организовал Хан Мигу Тимур её
founded it Yes they start there this city
основал Да они там начинают это города
was not there everything yes the Turks founded all the
не было там всё да тюрки основали все
cities in Muscovy this all the cities of
города в московии этой все города
Muscovy and Moscow paid tribute to the Turks
московии и Москва платила Дань тюркам
always always
всегда всегда
So Yes it's good Guys let's
Так что Да это хорошо Ребята давайте
no no no And wait what about Kiev
нене не А подожди а то что Киев был
Kiev was the capital of Rus' yes yes and
столицей Киев столицей Руси был да да а
Moscow Moscow is not Rus' Moscow is not
Москва Москва - это не Русь Москва не
Rus' Well, initially
Русь Ну изначально же оттуда не смотри я
from there don't look I'll explain to you Look, Rus, they say now Rus, it was from Kyiv, Moscow - it was on the ku, here Imagine that there was the Soviet Union Yes, no, then there was no Soviet Union, so Moscow, when there was Kievan Rus, Moscow was there there was a swamp they were here are the Slavs Yes Po I am in Ukraine when Kyiv existed Moscow was a swamp Yes there was a swamp Yes in general and there were cities Yes in modern Kazakhstan Kyrgyzstan Uzbekistan ancient cities were when Moscow did not exist at all Look in Uzbekistan there were poets yes When in Moscow in general writing naku city was yes in short we had cities Yes so guys Thank you very much Just pure in heart because I am three I am half Ukrainian half Kirz vyva we are like 2 with Kirghiz and half Ukrainian you have a great conversation Pek b all brother like squeak comment Write to my Telegram right now axis VN and Popik this is very and very important YouTube driving us through the scarg ORV in  your ban and
загоняя нас через скарг ОРВ в твый бан и
very many videos I don't show to people sometimes I
дуже багато видео не показу людям вчасно
don't show information about streams That's
не показуе информация про стрими Тому
why we Mali operational links
для того щоб ми Мали оперативний звязок
are written right now and while there in telegram
пишиться прямо зараз а пок там в телегра
OKM videos there are also interesting and useful
окм видео ще теж цикава и корисна
information and we will contact you timely
информация и ми пови з вами тримати пой
operational links
оперативний звязок
independently in  that will show you the process
незалежно в того покаже вам проце
YouTube Slava ukrai letter
YouTube Слава украи пись
with
с